

EVAN HIGGINS

Student | University of Limerick

PROFILE

My name is Evan Higgins. I am 24 vears old and currently in my first year of studying Computer Science in the University of Limerick. I have been studying programming for 3 years prior to this, being self-thought through programming literature and the use of online courses, such as those supplied by Udemy and Harvard's CS50. I am a driven and motivated person who has an extensive history of employment within the entertainment and hospitality sector since the age of 18. From this, I have a strong work ethic, approaching obstacles with a "do now, not later" attitude. I have a great eve for detail, assisting in the marketing side of business while employed as a Duty Manager within VUE (formerly Showtime) Cinema Limerick. I am a dedicated, loval employee who works well within teams, putting a high focus on efficiency through time management and task delegation.

CONTACT

PHONE: 083 041 2042

EMAIL:

evan.higgins@live.com

CITHUR

https://github.com/evanhiggins0/

HOBBIES

Sports Music Film

EDUCATION

University of Limerick

03/09/2020 – Currently BSc. In Computer Science

University of Limerick

06/09/2019 – 30/05/2020 Mature Student Access Certificate

St. Caimin's Community School

01/09/2009 - 01/07/2014 Leaving Certificate

Udemy

Completed courses in C, Python and Java development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Showtime Cinema/VUE Cinema Limerick – Duty Manager 01/06/2016 – 20/08/2019

Full time management position within a major cinema in Limerick. Responsibilities including customer service, daily management of staff and delegation of tasks, stock control and delivery management, BackOffice suite utilization and roster creation. A high level of time management and a keen eye for detail was required for this role. Departed role to begin full time education.

Showtime Cinema Limerick - Floor Staff

06/02/2015 - 30/05/2016

Full time customer facing role within a major cinema in Limerick.

SKILLS

- Java programming
- ICT software experience
- Leadership
- Time management
- Interpersonal communication
- Professionalism
- Problem solving aptitude
- Pressure situations